And then finally, our last setup is going to be using a tool called Git pod
最后一个我们可选的工具是 Gitpod
starting from Lesson five. The lesson that we're on right now, ethers, jazz, simple storage,
从第五章开始，就是我们现在正在进行这一章 "Ethers.js Simple Storage"
all of our code repos are going to come with a button
我们所有的代码仓库都会带有一个按钮
in the repo scroll down,
在仓库内向下滚动
they'll come with this open in get pod button.
它们都会附带一个 "Open in Gitpod"(在 Gitpod 中打开) 按钮
Now git pod is a cloud development environment
Gitpod 是一种云开发环境
where you can actually run your code on a remote server,
它可以让你在远程服务器上运行你的代码
it's kind of similar to remix IDE,
有些类似于 Remix IDE
but it allows you to run Visual Studio code in the browser or connected to another server.
不过它只是允许你在浏览器上或是以连接到其他服务器的方式运行 Visual Studio Code
This is good because then you don't have to do any installation on anything.
这很不错，因为这样你就不用安装各种东西了
Since all the tools that you can want to use are just going to be running on this remote server.
因为你要使用的所有工具都会在这个远程服务器上运行
This has its downsides, though, obviously,
但是它的缺点也很明显
since you'll only be able to code if git pod is up and working for you.
因为你只有在 Gitpod 启动并正常工作时才能编写代码
Additionally, when it comes to private keys,
此外，当涉及私钥时
you absolutely do not want to run any code with a private key that has real money in good pop.
你肯定不想用一个有真金白银的私钥在 Gitpod 上运行代码
Why? Well, once again,
为什么？
since you're running your scripts on a remote server,
因为你是在远程服务器上运行的你的脚本
those servers have access to your private keys.
所以这些服务器可以访问你的私钥
But since you've Pinky promise that for this course, you're not going to be using a meta mask or a private key with actual money in it,
但是既然你都向本课程拉钩承诺过，你不会往 MetaMask 或私钥中放真钱
it should be fine.
所以这应该也不是什么大问题
The other downside is that these often cost money to use and get pot isn't free.
另一个缺点是使用这些工具通常需要花钱，Gitpod 并不是免费的
But it's an option if you absolutely cannot get any of the installation working.
但这仍然不失为一种选择，如果你确实没法进行工具的安装
So if you go ahead and you hit this opening get pod button,
所以如果你继续并点击了这个 "Open in Gitpod" 按钮
you'll get a welcome to get pods showing up.
你就可以看到这个 "Welcome to Gitpod" 的界面
We're gonna go ahead and continue with GitHub.
我们继续在这里选择 "Continue with GitHub"
Since you've signed up for GitHub here,
因为你已经注册过了 Github
you want to go ahead and authorize get pod.
你需要继续并授权给 Gitpod
And it'll go ahead and start creating this workspace for you.
接着它就会开始为你创建工作区
And you'll notice it looks exactly like Visual Studio Code.
你会发现它看起来和 Visual Studio Code 一模一样
Since I opened the repo up in Git pod, it came with all the code,
因为我在 Gitpod 中打开了代码仓库，所以这里附带了所有的代码
and you can even open this workspace up in VS code desktop.
你甚至可以在桌面 VS Code 中打开这个工作区
So this is might be a little bit confusing.
不过这可能会让人感到有些迷惑
But basically, you can run off of Git pod using your local Visual Studio code.
不过基本上来说，你是可以用本地的 Visual Studio Code 来运行 Gitpod 的
And if you see git pod here, that's how you know that you're running off of Git pod.
如果你在这个地方看到了 gitpod，就表明你是在通过 Gitpod 运行
If you see this pop up,
如果你看到了这个弹窗
do you want to open this workspace in VS code desktop, you can hit Open.
“你想要使用桌面 VS Code 打开此工作区么”，你可以点击 "Open"
And it'll ask you if you want to open up Visual Studio Code,
它就会询问你是否想要打开 Visual Studio Code
which I'm going to go ahead and hit yes.
我们继续并选择“是的”
And you'll get something that looks like this on your Visual Studio Code.
接着你就会在你的 Visual Studio Code 里得到类似这样的东西
It'll tell you that it wants to install the Git pod extension, and then open that Git pod URL.
它会询问你是否想要安装 Gitpod 扩展并打开 Gitpod 链接
So you can go ahead and install it.
所以你可以选择继续并安装它
Reload window and open
选择“重新启动窗口并打开”
and it's going to go ahead and start connecting to our the Git pod workspace.
然后它就会开始连接到我们的 Gitpod 工作区
And this is going to be the same as running git pod in the browser here.
这种方式和在浏览器里运行 Gitpod 是一样
Or you can also do it manually by hitting the Git pod in the bottom left,
或者你可以手动点击左下角的 Gitpod 按钮
and then type in open in VS code
然后输入 "Open in VS Code"
And then you should be able to run it in your Visual Studio code.
然后你就可以在 Visual Studio Code 中运行它了
For now, I'm going to recommend that if you're using Git pod, just stay in the browser,
目前，如果你使用的是 Gitpod，那么我建议你留在浏览器内
just so that you know, okay,
这只是为了时刻提醒你
I am running this on a remote server. And just as a reminder for you that you're not actually locally developing.
现在是在远程服务器上运行，而不是在本地进行开发
And hopefully, this will be a trigger to not actually put
希望这可以提醒你
any special private keys or anything like that.
不要往上面放任何私钥之类的东西
But you can make workspaces, you can make new folders,
不过你可以新建工作区，新建文件夹
and you should be able to run all the commands on here,
并且应该能够运行这里的所有命令
as if you are running locally with Visual Studio code.
就好像你在本地运行 Visual Studio Code 一样
To open up the terminal, you can hit this little bar at the top left,
要想打开终端，可以点击左上角这个小栏
go to terminal, new terminal, or use CTRL tilde
再点击 "Terminal", "New Terminal" 或者使用 CTRL + ~
exact same as Mac OS and Linux keyboard shortcuts
就和 Mac OS 以及 Linux 的键盘快捷键完全相同
to create a new folder, we can change directory, CD, dot.mk, dir, new folder,
要想创建一个新的文件夹，我们可以更改目录 "cd .." "mkdir new_folder"
MK dir makes make directory called New Folder.
"mkdir" 就是新建一个文件夹，名为 "new_folder"
And then we're going to change our directory into a new folder, and hit enter.
然后我们要改变我们的目录到 new_folder 下，敲击回车
And now we're in that new folder.
现在我们就是在 new_folder 里了
For each section, you can either open up the entire source code right into GitHub,
对于每个章节，你都可以直接在 Gitpod 中打开整个源代码
or you can create a new folder for each section yourself and start from blank.
或者你可以自己为每个章节创建一个新的文件夹并从头开始
And then you would just type code period.
你只需要输入 "code ."
And you'd be in a brand new folder.
然后你就是在一个全新的文件夹里了